Guide to the Guerrilla TV Archive 1965-1997 MSS 138 MSS.138
Fales Library and Special Collections
Guerrilla TV Archive
1965-2007
Fales Library and Special Collections
Boyle, Deirdre
MSS.138
17 Linear Feet in 20 containers
The Guerrilla TV Archive contains files, publicity information, audiocassettes, printed materials and photographs relating to Deirdre Boyle's research for the book Subject to Change: Guerrilla Television Revisited and some materials related to her work on other publications and projects including Hong Kong Cinema, Video Classics, and Video Preservation.
Provenance
Deirdre Boyle donated the Guerrilla TV Archive to Fales Library and Special Collections in July 2003.
Access Restrictions
Materials are open to researchers. Please contact the Fales Library and Special Collections, fales.library@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596.
Biographical Note
Deirdre Boyle is a video historian and media critic as well as a programmer, consultant and media preservation advocate. She received her Master's degree in Media Studies from Antioch College and currently is a senior core faculty member in the Graduate Media Studies Program at New School University. Deirdre Boyle received the New School's Distinguished Teaching Award in 1998. She also received a Fulbright Fellowship to study in Moscow in 1992 and an Ace Award for Best Documentary Series on Cable TV in 1988. As these awards indicate, Deirdre Boyle has remarkable expertise as a documentary historian, teacher and researcher.
Additionally, Deirdre Boyle is an accomplished author. She frequently contributes articles to notable popular and scholarly video, film and television journals including Afterimage, ARTnews, Cineaste, The Independent, Journal of Film and Video, Television Quarterly, Wide Angle and The Village Voice. This archive represents Deirdre Boyle's research for her 1997 book Subject to Change: Guerrilla Television Revisited for which she was awarded a Guggenheim Fellowship and support from the New York State Council on the Arts (NYSCA). In addition to this book, she has published two other books on video, Video Classics: A Guide to Video Art and Documentary Tape (1986) and Video Preservation: Ensuring the Future of the Past (1993).
Finally, Deirdre Boyle is an active organizer of video art and documentary exhibitions for museums, libraries, film festivals and universities throughout the world. Most notably, the Museum of Modern Art in New York, The Brussels Video Festival and the Hong Kong Arts Centre invited her to guest curate video art exhibitions.
Deirdre Boyle was and remains an important figure in the field of video, television and film through her work as a teacher, author and organizer. Her contribution to video arts, history and preservation is particularly significant. This archive represents a cross section of Deirdre Boyle's interests and is an especially valuable resource for anyone interested in the development of the medium and technology of video.
Scope and Content Note
The Guerrilla TV Archive primarily reflects Deirdre Boyle's research for the book Subject to Change: Guerrilla Television Revisited. The guerrilla TV movement began in the late 1960s with the commercial release and marketing of the portable video camera. The archive documents the growing accessiblity of video technology and the rise of video collectives committed to using videotape as an artistic, storytelling, documentary, and socially transforming medium. Additionally, the archive shows the development of video preservation concerns, the rise of video collections within public and academic research libraries and the connections between underground video, cable and corporate television networks.
The archive is particularly rich in personal interviews between Deirdre Boyle and many influential individuals such as Skip Blumberg, Allen Rucker, Wendy Apple, and Michael Shamberg, who were involved in video collectives such as Top Value Television (TVTV), the Videofreex, New Orleans Public Access Cable, and Broadside TV, among many others. The materials span the mid-1960s through the early 1990s offering a comprehensive view of the guerrilla tv movement and activist media, in general, through interviews, articles, publications, photographs and publicity materials.
Documentary film and video, as an activist genre, is also reflected in the collection through interviews with John Reilly and Julie Gustafson of Global Village, programs for documentary film festivals as well as interviews with filmmaker George Stoney. Another strength of the collection is documentation of the development of video technology. The archive contains materials that document and publicize developments in portable video technology, including materials relating to satellite technology, videotaping and editing, the beginnings of cable television and numerous manuals, magazines and catalogues reflecting the cutting edge of video technology of the time.
The collection also contains a small amount of materials relating to Deirdre Boyle's other interests in video and film. These materials include festival catalogues and programs from Hong Kong Cinema, documentation of video preservation concerns and philosophy as well as video art exhibition catalogues.
Arrangement
Materials have been kept in the order created by Deirdre Boyle.
Series I, Files are arranged by subject.
Series II, Videologs for Subject to Change are arranged alphabetically with miscellaneous videologs appearing at the end of the series. Videologs for Video Classics appear together at the beginning of the series.
Series III, Notes are arranged sequentially, as they were originally numbered by Deirdre Boyle, and by material type.
Series IV, contains interview transcripts arranged alphabetically by interviewee surname.
Series V, Photographs are grouped by publication and research project.
Series VI, Catalogues and Brochures are arranged alphabetically by sponsoring organization.
Series VII, Audiocassettes are divided into four subseries:
Subseries A contains interviews for Subject to Change: Guerrilla Television Revisited.
Subseries B is comprised of recordings of conferences arranged alphabetically by sponsoring organization.
Subseries C includes other interviews not specifically relating to any project or publication.
Subseries D contains interviews conducted by Deirdre Boyle on a trip to Australia in 1995.
Series VIII, Printed Materials is organized into 3 subseries: Subseries A, Books, Studies and Reports; Subseries B, Periodicals; Subseries C, Hong Kong International Film Festival Materials. Materials in each subseries are arranged alphabetically by author.
Series I: Files
Series II: Videologs
Series III: Notes
Series IV: Interview Transcripts
Series V: Photographs
Series VI: Catalogues and Brochures
Series VII: Audiocassettes
Series VII: Printed Materials
Oversize - Series I: Files
Oversize - Series V: Photographs
Oversize - Series VIIIB: Printed Materials
Related Material at Fales Library and Special Collections
The Jaime Davidovich Collection, MSS 155
Women's Independent Film Exchange Collection, [ca. 1950s-1980s]
Separated Material
Printed materials from the Guerrilla TV Archive Library have been separated and individually catalogued into Fales' Downtown Collection. Call numbers for these items can be located through Bobcat.
Armstrong, David. A Trumpet to Arms: Alternative Media in America, 1981.
Afterimage: The Journal of Media Arts and Cultural Criticism. 2:7, 3:1-10, May-June 1976, 4:1-5, 5:5, 6:1, 6:2, 6:4, 6:6, 7:3, 7:7, 9:5, 11:1-10, 12:1-10, 13:1-10, 14:1-2, 15:3-10, 16:1-10, 17:1-10, 18:1-10, 24:2, 24:5, 24:6, 25:2.
Aspen Institute for Humanistic Studies. Expanding the Choices for Television Viewing: A report from a Communications Policy Workshop, 1981.
Baer, Walter S. Cable Television: A Handbook for Decision Making, 1974.
Bateson, Gregory. Steps to an Ecology of Mind: A Revolutionary Approach to Man's Understanding of Himself, 1976.
The Bay Area Video Coalition. Needs Assessment and Feasibility Study.
Bell, Daniel. Toward the Year 2000: Work in Progress, 1968.
Blum, John Morton. Years of Discord: American Politics and Society, 1961-1974, 1991.
Carnegie Commission. A Public Trust: The Report of the Carnegie Commission on the Future of Public Broadcasting, 1979.
Carroll, Peter N. It Seemed Like Nothing Happened: The Tragedy and Promise of America in the 1970s, 1982.
Cater, Douglass., ed. Television as a Social Force: New Approaches to TV Criticism, 1975.
Chimaera Monagraphie: Lynn Hershman, 1992.
Contents Magazine, photocopy of Pilot issue.
Costello, Marjorie and Michael Heiss. How to Select and Use Home Video Equipment, 1984.
Crouse, Timothy. The Boys on the Bus, 1973.
Dubin, Morton Donald. A Videotape Glossary: A Practical Guide to Understanding the Professional Videotape Business.
Foundation of Independent Video and Film. Report: the 1979 National Conference of Media Arts Centers, 1979.
Fuller, R. Buckminster. Operating Manual for Spaceship Earth, 1970.
Gill, Johanna. Video: State of the Art. Working Papers of the Rockefeller Foundation, 1976.
The Global Village Handbook for Independent Producers. A Guide to Public Television and the New Media. 2nd ed., 1981.
Goldstein, Neil. Alternative Television: Status, trends and issues, 1974.
Hoffman, Abbie. Steal This Book, 1982.
The Independent: Film and Video Monthly. [selected issues] 1979-2001.
Independent Television-Makers and Public Communications Policy, Working Papers of the Rockefeller Foundation, 1979.
Levine, Faye. The Culture Barons: An Analysis of Power and Money in the Arts, 1976.
Lyons, Nick., The Sony Vision, 1976.
Johnson, Nicholas. How to Talk Back to Your Television Set, 1970.
Mack, Theresa. Portable Video Documentary: An Historical Perspective, 1976.
MediaArts, issues 1:1-12, 2:5-6, 1983.
Murray, Michael. The Videotape Book: A Basic Guide to Portable TV Production for Families, Friends, Schools and Neighborhoods, 1975.
National Endowment for the Arts. Toward Civilization: Overview from a Report on Arts Education, 1988.
Nielson Report on Television, 1980.
Roszak, Theodore. The Making of a Counter Culture: Reflections on the Technocratic Society and its Youthful Opposition, 1969.
Shamberg, Michael and Raindance Corporation. Guerrilla Television, 1971.
Sinard, Craig Paul. Television and Video Access, 1979.
Sloan Commission. On the Cable: The Television of Abundance, a Report of the Sloan Commission on Cable Communications, 1971.
Smith, Ralph Lee. The Wired Nation, 1972.
Television: International Exchange of Cultural Programming, A Bellagio Conference. Working Papers of the Rockefeller Foundation, 1978.
Thompson, Hunter S. Fear and Loathing: On the Campaign Trail '72, 1983.
The Video Handbook, 2nd Ed., 1974.
Videodance: a Notebook from ARC Videodance.
Wolfe, Tom. The New Journalism, 1973.
Radical Software, Contents, Videocity, 1:1-5 [photocopies of 1:1-4, originals of 1:3-5] 2:1, 2:4-6, 1970-1974.
Satellite Video Exchange. #8, 2:4, 2:5, 3:2, 5:1, 5:2, November 1978- January 1979.
Send: Video Communication Arts [Formerly Video Eighties] Summer-Fall 1983, Spring 1984, Spring 1985.
Video 80-1. 1:1, 1:2, #4, 1980-1981.
Video 81. 2:1, 1981.
Video Eighties, 1982-1983.
TeleVisions [formerly Community Video Report] 3:1-4, 4:1-3, 5:1-4, 6:1-4, 7:1-4, 8:1-2.
Videoscope: Incorporating Radical Software. 1:1-4, 2:1.
Hong Kong Cinema publications
A Study of the Hong Kong Swordplay Film (1945-1980). The Fifth Hong Kong International Film Festival. City Hall Lecture Hall. April 9-24 1981.
Cantonese Cinema Retrospective (1960-1969). Revised Edition. The Sixth Hong Kong International Film Festival. Space Museum Lecture Hall. April 1-16, 1982.
A Study of Hong Kong Cinema in the Seventies. The Eighth Hong Kong International Film Festival. April 12-27, 1984.
Cantonese Melodrama 1950-1969. The Tenth Hong Kong International Film Festival. March 27-April 11, 1986.
Cantonese Opera Film Retrospective. The Eleventh Hong Kong International Film Festival. April 10-25, 1987.
Phantoms of the Hong Kong Cinema. The Thirteenth Hong Kong International Film Festival. March 23-April 7, 1989.
The China Factor in Hong Kong Cinema. The Fourteenth Hong Kong International Film Festival. April 6-21, 1990.
Overseas Chinese Figures in Cinema. The Sixteenth Hong Kong International Film Festival. April 10-25, 1992.
Mandarin Films and Popular Songs 40's-60's. The Seventeenth Hong Kong International Film Festival. April 8-24, 1993.
Cinema of Two Cities: Hong Kong-Shanghai. The Eighteenth Hong Kong International Film Festival. March 25-April 4, 1994.
Early Images of Hong Kong and China. The Nineteenth Hong Kong International Film Festival. April 7-22 1995.
The Restless Breed: Cantonese Stars of the Sixties. The Twentieth Hong Kong International Film Festival. March 25-April 19, 1996.
Fifty Years of Electric Shadows. The Twenty-First Hong Kong International Film Festival. March 25-April 4, 1997.
Hong Kong Panorama 96-97. The Twenty-First Hong Kong International Film Festival, 1997.
(1947-1997)50 Years of the Hong Kong Film Production and Distribution Industries: An Exhibition, 1997.
Hong Kong Films 1993.
Hong Kong Film Archive Newsletter. [also called "HKFA Newsletter" and "Newsletter"] Nos. 7, 9-19, 21-24.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
The audiovisual materials in the collection were digitized by the Barbara Goldsmith Preservation and Conservation Department in 2018. Digital access copies are available by appointment for reading room viewing and listening only. Please contact fales.library@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596.
Newsletters.; Posters.; Photographs.; Minneapolis (Minn.); Videocassettes.; Video recordings -- Social aspects.; Notes.; Transcripts.; New Orleans (La.); Audiocassettes.; Public television -- United States.; Public-access television -- United States; Correspondence.; Documentary television programs.; Video recordings |x Political aspects.; Exhibition catalogs.; Video art |v Periodicals.; Los Angeles (Calif.); New York (N.Y.).; Files.; Serials (publications); Books.; Correspondence.; Clippings (information artifacts); Video art.; Apple, Wendy; Videofreex (Production company); Top Value Television (Production company); Rucker, Allen; New Orleans Video Access Center; Stoney, George C.; Shamberg, Michael; Broadside TV; Blumberg, Skip; Global Village (Firm); Gigliotti, Davidson; TVTV (Production company); Boyle, Deirdre
- Series I: Files
  Scope and Contents note
  The first series contains research materials for the book, Subject to Change. Contents include clippings, posters, correspondence, resumes, photographs and notes organized by organization or individual names.
  - Alan and Susan Raymond, 1977-1982 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - People's Video Theatre - Woodstock Community Video, 1976-1984 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Nancy Cain, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Tom Zafian, 1978-1983 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Johnny Videotape (H.Allen Frederikson) Community Video Access, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Community Video (Misc. groups), 1977-1981 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Washington Community Video Center, undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Videopolis, ca. 1977 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Urban Planning Aid Boston, undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - John Reilly (Global Village), 1975-1984 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Los Angeles Public Access, undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Larry Kirkman, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Thea Sklover, Open Channel, 1972-1983 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - SWAMP (Southwest Alternate Media Project), 1982-1985 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - D. Visions, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Image Atlanta, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - 1st annual Global Village Documentary Festival, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - 2nd annual Global Village Documentary Festival, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - 3rd annual Global Village Documentary Festival, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - 4th annual Global Village Documentary Festival, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - 5th annual Global Village Documentary Festival, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - 6th annual Global Village Documentary Festival, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - 7th annual Global Village Documentary Festival, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - 8th annual Global Village Documentary Festival, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - 10th annual Global Village Documentary Festival, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - 11th annual Global Village Documentary Festival, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - 12th annual Global Village Documentary Festival, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Global Village, 1983-1986 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Asian American Video Festival, undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Anthology Film Archives, 1978-1986 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Athens Video Festival, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Athens Video Festival, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 32A)
  - Athens Video Festival, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 32B)
  - Athens Video Festival, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Perspectives on Community Video DCTV Festival, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - DCTV Community Video Festival, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Whitney Museum Video [article "The Whitney Museum and the Shaping of Video Art: An Interview with John Hanhardt", by Marita Sturken], 1983 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Cindy Furlong, Image Processing, 1981-1983 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Marita [Sturken] - EAI Video essay and bibliography, ca. 1986 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - American Film Institute (AFI) National Video Festival, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - AFI National Video Festival, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - AFI National Video Festival, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Library of Congress Video Holdings, 1978-1982 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Vanderbilt TV News Archive, ca. 1977 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Museum of Modern Art (MoMA) Video Publicity, 1974-1987 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Whitney Video Publicity, 1978-1987 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Miscellaneous Video Exhibitions, 1980-1986 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - The Kitchen, Fliers, Publicity etc., 1977-1986 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Long Beach Museum Video Publicity, 1980-1987 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - New York State Council on the Arts (NYSCA), ca. 1984 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - National Endowment for the Arts (NEA), 1972-1983 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Rockefeller Foundation, H. Klein, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - WGBH Boston, 1977-1980 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - WXXI Rochester, NY, 1979-1981 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Funding, 1970-1986 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - The Television Laboratory at Thirteen, 1972-1982 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - The Television Laboratory at Thirteen, Report '75, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Independent Documentary Fund (IDF) and TV Lab, 1973-1983 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Bay Area Video Coalition (BAVC), 1979-1983 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Women's Video, 1974-1986 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Susan Milano, 1973-1980 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Cara DeVito, undated (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Elle Anthony, 1973-1980 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Bill Stephens, 1978-1986 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Philip Jones, 1978-1981 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - St. Clair Bourne, 1983-1988 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Michelle Parkerson, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Disarmament Video Survey, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Doug Kellner, Alternative Views (Austin Cable TV Show), 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Dan Reeves, 1981-1987 (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Edin Velez, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Fred Simon, 1979-1985 (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Skip Blumberg, 1979-1985 (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Shirley Clarke, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 73A)
  - Wendy Clarke, 1980-1984 (Box 2, Folder 73B)
  - Stevenson Palfi, 1982-1984 (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - James Morris, 1979-1983 (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Dennis Darmek, 1979-1986 (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Mike Hazard, 1982-1986 (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - Barbara Buckner, 1978-1981 (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - Dara Birnbaum, 1982-1986 (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - Peter D'Agostino, 1975-1983 (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - Juan Downey, 1977-1984 (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - Fitzgerald and Sanborn, ca. 1982 (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - Shalom Gorewitz, ca. 1986 (Box 2, Folder 83)
  - Mitchell Kriegman, ca. 1979 (Box 2, Folder 84)
  - Miscellaneous Video Art, 1979-1988 (Box 2, Folder 85)
  - Video Artists A-L, 1984-1986 (Box 2, Folder 86)
  - Video Artists M-Z, 1979-1986 (Box 2, Folder 87)
  - V Tape Video Reference Guide, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 88)
  - Canadian Video, 1974-1981 (Box 3, Folder 89)
  - Canadian Video Articles, 1980-1988 (Box 3, Folder 90)
  - Alvarez, Kolker and New Orleans Video Access Center (NOVAC), 1977-1982 (Box 3, Folder 91)
  - Jon Alpert, 1978-1999 (Box 3, Folder 92)
  - Jon Alpert articles and catalogues, 1978-1996 (Box 3, Folder 93)
  - Ant Farm, 1972-2003 (Box 3, Folder 94)
  - Appalshop, 1975-1983 (Box 3, Folder 95)
  - (Video) Bibliography, 1976-1978 (Box 3, Folder 96)
  - Broadside TV, 1971-1984 (Box 3, Folder 97)
  - Challenge for Change, 1968-1992 (Box 3, Folder 98)
  - Maxi Cohen, ca. 1985 (Box 3, Folder 99)
  - Chronologies - Video History, ca. 1983 (Box 3, Folder 100)
  - Specific Chronology - Video History Project, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 101)
  - Downsville TV, Dean and Dudley Evenson, undated (Box 3, Folder 102)
  - Ralph Engleman - Origins of Public Access and Cable Television 1966-1972., undated (Box 3, Folder 103)
  - Flippen, Charles C. "Liberating the Media: The New Journalism, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 104)
  - Arthur Ginsburg "Carol and Ferd" (see also Video Free America), ca. 1975 (Box 3, Folder 105)
  - Guerrilla TV Symposium, Anthology Film Archives, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 106)
  - Todd Gitlin - "Sixteen Notes on TV and the Movement" notes on "The Whole World is Watching", 1972 (Box 3, Folder 107)
  - John Godfrey interview with Skip Blumberg, ca. 1983 (Box 3, Folder 108)
  - Chris Hill and Hallwalls History, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 109)
  - Ithaca Video Festival, 1981-1995 (Box 3, Folder 110)
  - Beryl Korot, 1974-1980 (Box 3, Folder 111)
  - Edward Charles Kurtz, Jr. MA thesis "A Case History: Developing 'Survival Information Television' in New Orleans", 1982 (Box 3, Folder 112)
  - Daniel Francis Mangin MA Thesis "A Critical Approach to Video Artworks", 1983 (Box 3, Folder 113)
  - Mobius Video, San Francisco, 1974-1979 (Box 3, Folder 114)
  - National Federation of Local Cable Programmers and Community Television Review (NFLCP and CTR), 1986 (Box 3, Folder 115)
  - New Orleans Video Access Center (NOVAC), 1972-1992 (Box 3, Folder 116)
  - NOVAC Cable Proposal, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 117)
  - National Video Resources (NVR) Reports, 1991-1996 (Box 3, Folder 118)
  - Obituaries - Video [Howard Wise], 1989 (Box 3, Folder 119)
  - John O'Connor - New York Times Articles, 1979-1983 (Box 3, Folder 120)
  - Optic Nerve, 1977-1981 (Box 3, Folder 121)
  - Paper Tiger TV, Deep Dish TV and DeeDee Halleck, 1982-1991 (Box 3, Folder 122)
  - People's Video Theatre, 1970, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 123)
  - Portable Channel, 1974-1984 (Box 4, Folder 124)
  - Port Washington Public Library Video - Lillian Katz (folder 1 of 3), 1982-1992 (Box 4, Folder 125)
  - Port Washington Public Library (folder 2 of 3), 1972-1983 (Box 4, Folder 126)
  - Port Washington Public Library (folder 3 of 3), 1971-1973 (Box 4, Folder 127)
  - Public Interest Video Network, 1979-1984 (Box 4, Folder 128)
  - Review "Uncovering the Sixties" by Abe Peck, New Republic, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 129)
  - Raindance, 1972-1991 (Box 4, Folder 130)
  - J. Rosenbaum and Early Videotape Sources, 1976-1984 (Box 4, Folder 131)
  - Paul Ryan, 1979-1988 (Box 4, Folder 132)
  - San Francisco Video Festival, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 133)
  - Ira Schneider, 1980-1981 (Box 4, Folder 134)
  - George Stoney, 1972-2000 (Box 4, Folder 135)
  - Social Context, Communes etc., 1972-1979 (Box 4, Folder 136)
  - Sony, 1976-1984 (Box 4, Folder 137)
  - Parry Teasdale, 1993-1996 (Box 4, Folder 138)
  - (Early Video) Technology, 1970-1984 (Box 4, Folder 139)
  - Top Value Television (TVTV), 1973-1992 (Box 4, Folder 140)
  - TVTV Conventions, 1972-1984 (Box 4, Folder 141)
  - TVTV Lord of the Universe, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 142)
  - TVTV In Hiding, Abbie Hoffman, 1975-1989 (Box 4, Folder 143)
  - TVTV Gerald Ford's America, ca. 1975 (Box 4, Folder 144)